kaorisan.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy - Kaori-san

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Kaori-san collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the www.kaorisan.com website and its mobile app.

### ■ Personal identification information

Users may be asked for, as appropriate, personal identification information such as name, phone number,email address, and mailing address . We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. If users sign in with Google or Facebook, we may also collect basic information, friends list and email address.  
Please learn more about their privacy policies on their websites.

### ■ Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information such as IP address and technical information about users means of connection to our site to improve our services.

### ■ How we store and use information

Our primary purpose in collecting your personal identification information is to provide you with the services you request. You agree that we may use your information primarily for the virtual assistant services or to support your request and to improve our customer service.  
We do not sell, trade, rent, or disclose users personal identification information to others except for our business partners.  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure or destruction of your personal information.  
If you supply information with a request such as mobile phone number, this information is saved in such a way that it is not accessible to any other assistants than the assigned assistant working on your request.  
Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information or delete what they have already submitted, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.  
We do not collect or store users credit card number on our server and no assistants or administrators can access such information.

### ■ Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer’s hard disk. Like many websites, we use cookies to collect additional website usage data and to enhance user experience. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them before accepting a cookie.

### ■ How we may disclose users information

We may disclose users personal identification information to enforce our policies, or where we are permitted to do so by applicable law, such as in response to a request by a law enforcement or governmental authority, or in connection with actual or proposed litigation, or to protect our property, people and other rights or interests.

### ■ Changes to this privacy policy

We may revise this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on Kaori-san’s website.

### ■ Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please email us at [support@kaorisan.com](mailto:support@kaorisan.com)
